ever since I killed those three wall
street guys
okay I'm waiting for the punch line
there is no point I'm [ __ ]
it's not a joke [ __ ]
you're serious aren't you you're telling
us you killed those three young men on
the subway
and why should we believe you because
I’ve got nothing else to lose
nothing can hurt me anymore
my life is a comedy
let me get this straight you think that
killing those guys is funny
i do and I'm tired of pretending it's
not
comedy is subjective murray isn't that
what they say and [ __ ]
all of you this system that knows so
much
you decide what's right or wrong
the same way you decide what's funny
or not
okay I think I i might understand that
you
did this to start a movement to become a
symbol come on [ __ ] do I look like the
kind of clown who could start a movement
i killed those guys because they were
awful everybody is
awful these days it's enough to make
everyone crazy and [ __ ]
you're crazy that's your defense for
killing three young men
no they couldn't carry a tune to save
their lives
oh why is everyone upset about these
guys
if it was me down on the street you'd
walk right over me
i'll pass you every day and you don't
notice me these guys what because thomas
when cried about them on tv
you have a problem with thomas wayne yes
i do
have you seen what it's like out there
moray
do you ever actually leave the studio
everybody just yells and screams at each
other
nobody's civil anymore nobody thinks
about what it's like to be the other
guy you think man like thomas wayne
everything was like do you think someone
like me
will be somebody like themselves they
don't
they think that would just sit there and
take it like poopy baby [ __ ]
that we won't wear or go wild and [ __ ]
i mean there's so much self-pity out
there you sound like you're making
excuses for killing those young men
not everybody and i'll tell you this not
everyone is awful
you're awesome me I'm awful
oh yeah how am I awful
playing my video and [ __ ] inviting me on
the show
you just want to make fun of me you're
just like the rest of them
you don't know the first thing about me
pal look what happened because of what
you did
what it led to there were riots out
there two policemen are in critical
condition
i know
how about another joke mariah
do you get when you cross a mentally ill
with a society
who abandons him and treats him like
trash
i'll tell you what you get you get what
you [ __ ] deserve
[ __ ]
[Applause]
hahahahahahahahahaha